<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>eGPU on goParker</title>
    <link>https://goparker.com/tags/egpu/</link>
    <description>Recent content in eGPU on goParker</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2012 09:55:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://goparker.com/tags/egpu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My DIY eGPU Project – Speed boost</title>
      <link>https://goparker.com/post/2012-08-01-my-diy-egpu-project-speed-boost/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2012 09:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goparker.com/post/2012-08-01-my-diy-egpu-project-speed-boost/</guid>
      <description>This morning, some lovely person using the handle Burger commented on one of my earlier postssuggesting that if I connect the eGPU setup after boot-up is complete then I should get a significant boost due to PCIe compression. I little bit of Googling reveals a bit more detail here, but it seems that you need to have a ‘modern’ Intel integrated GPU in combination with one of a fairly narrow range of Nvidia kit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My DIY eGPU Project – The Hawk</title>
      <link>https://goparker.com/post/2012-07-31-my-diy-egpu-project-the-hawk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2012 22:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goparker.com/post/2012-07-31-my-diy-egpu-project-the-hawk/</guid>
      <description>Today my new graphics card arrived from eBay. It is a second hand MSI N460GTX Hawkwhich I picked up for a reasonable £79.02 including postage. This puts the running total for the eGPU project (not including bits that I had lying around) at £166.10.
So how does it perform? Well you may remember that I previously benchmarkedboth the integrated graphics of my laptop and a borrowed Geforce 9600GT in the eGPU adapter with the eGPU providing a splendid 3 times increase in the 3DMark06 score.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My DIY eGPU project – Benchmarking</title>
      <link>https://goparker.com/post/2012-07-26-my-diy-egpu-project-benchmarking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 22:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goparker.com/post/2012-07-26-my-diy-egpu-project-benchmarking/</guid>
      <description>Well, I have done a spot of benchmarking. Specifically using 3DMark06 and the Resident Evil 5 benchmarking tool. If you are wondering what I am talking about here is an introductionand a follow-up.
I guess a brief recap wouldn’t be out of place. I have a laptop with integrated graphics. This severely limits the games that I can play. This makes me sad. I have read that I can put together an adapter that plugs in to the ExpressCard slot in my laptop that allows me to use a desktop GPU to power the graphics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My DIY eGPU Project – Delivery and Test</title>
      <link>https://goparker.com/post/2012-07-26-my-diy-egpu-project-delivery-and-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 16:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goparker.com/post/2012-07-26-my-diy-egpu-project-delivery-and-test/</guid>
      <description>Today (26th) the adapter parts for my eGPU project arrived from Taiwan. I paid for it on the 20th via PayPal and on the 24th the PayPal status was updated to let me know that my purchase had shipped with a DHL tracking number. I am pretty happy with the delivery time.
Something that I knew was a possibility, though was still slightly vexing, was an accompanying VAT charge from Customs amounting to £12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My DIY eGPU Project – Introduction</title>
      <link>https://goparker.com/post/2012-07-20-my-diy-egpu-project-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 12:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goparker.com/post/2012-07-20-my-diy-egpu-project-introduction/</guid>
      <description>The PC that I use for work (and play) is a Toshiba Portégé R700-160 laptop. It is a delightfully sleek and portable device that packs a pretty decent Intel Core i5-520M Processor into its tiny chassis. A (perhaps unavoidable) weakness of the machine is its graphics capability as it relies on the integrated Intel Graphics Media Accelerator HD GPU. It can just about manage Civilization V but anything more graphically intensive is a shuddering no-no.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>